It Might Get Loud is a documentary, music film directed by Davis Guggenheim.
A documentary on the electric guitar from the point of view of three
significant rock musicians: the Edge, Jimmy Page and Jack White.
Self, played by Jimmy Page.
Self, played by The Edge.
Self, played by Jack White.
Self (archive footage), played by Link Wray.
It Might Get Loud is a 2008 American documentary
film by filmmaker Davis Guggenheim.
It explores the careers and musical styles of prominent rock
guitarists Jimmy Page, the Edge, and Jack White.
The film premiered at the 2008 Toronto International Film Festival, and received a wide
release in the United States on August 14, 2009, by Sony Pictures Classics.
The film explores themes of guitar, interview,
guitar player, rockumentary, virtuoso.